Will Sentance: 这里我们从 JavaScript 的原理开始。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So here we start
with principles of JavaScript.
所有这些奇妙的东西，所有这些深奥的东西,
All of this fancy stuff to come,
all of this profundity to come,
但是我们从 JavaScript 的原理开始。
but we start with
principles of JavaScript.
我要说的就是这些。
And I'll say this of all this.
你要看着代码，然后你要去是的，是的，是的,
You're gonna look at the code, and
you're gonna go yeah, yeah, yeah,
我知道这是怎么回事了。
I get what this is doing.
好了，伙计们，开始了。
All right, people, here we go.
并不是那么花哨。
JavaScript is not that fancy.
它有两个作用。
It does two things.
第一，它一行一行地检查我们的代码。
One, it goes through
our code line by line.
我们现在要处理一段代码。
There's a block of code we're
gonna work through right now.
它一行一行地检查代码，并执行每一行代码。
It go through it line by line and
does each of the lines of code.
他们称之为执行线程。
They call this the thread of execution.
它沿着它的路线下行并执行,
It threads its way down and executes,
这个词用来形容随机应变很好听。
that's a fancy word for
doing the code as it goes.
这是 JavaScript 的特性之一。
That's feature one of JavaScript.
Javascript 的第二个特性就是它遇到的东西
Feature two of JavaScript is
the stuff that it encounters
如果它说保存某个东西，比如变量或者常量
if it's saying save something,
like a variable or a constant, or
甚至一些代码本身，被称为函数。
even some code itself,
known as a function.
它把这些东西保存在电脑的内存里,
Well, it saves that stuff
in the computer's memory,
以后再回来，并使用。
to come back to later on, and use.
好了，这个区域，这里，各位，我要捕捉,
All right, and this area, here,
people, I'm gonna capture,
就像 JavaScript 在引擎盖下做的那样,
just as JavaScript does under the hood,
我们一行一行地检查代码时，存储的所有东西。
all of the stuff that's being stored
as we go through the code line by line.
这不是魔术,
This isn't like magic,
这不是我对现状的抽象描述。
this isn't me creating
an abstraction of what's happening.
这就是正在发生的事。
This is literally what's happening.
我的意思是，不明显，视觉上，但这是我们存储的每一行，我们去。
I mean, not obviously, visually, but
this is every line we store as we go.
这就是我们遇到的所有东西都被储存在记忆中。
And that's all that stuff we
encounter is stored into the memory.
这是 JavaScript 中的一个花哨的词
This is the fancy word in
JavaScript in partnering for
我们存储数据的地方。
the place in which we store data.
我们开始吧，谁有幸做第一行，是凯拉吗？
And so here we go, who is gonna have
the honor of doing line one, was it Kayla?
凯拉，一号线，我们要怎么处理这些代码，说给我听,
Kayla, line one, what are we doing with
that code here, verbalize it for me,
女名女子名。
Kayla.
演讲者2: 你在定义一个叫 num 的常量。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're defining
a constant called num.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 美丽，而且？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Beautiful, and?
演讲者2: 改变三。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Alter three.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 赋值3，就是人。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And assigning it
the value 3, there it is people.
这意味着从现在开始，如果你在我们的代码中看到 num，我们知道它会去查看,
That means from now on if you see num in
our code, we know that it's gonna go look,
然后找到它的价值是什么 Kayla？
and find the value, what, Kayla?
讲者2:3 威尔 · 森塔斯: 3，她说得很对。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: 3.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 3, she's spot-on.
为 Kayla 干杯作为第一个被邀请的人。
Excellent to Kayla, for
being the first person to be called upon.
下一行，我转向马特。
Next line, now I turn to Matt.
演讲者3: 我们正在定义函数，multiplyBy2。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We're defining the function,
multiplyBy2.
威尔 · 森特斯: 谢谢你，马特，非常感谢。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Thank you,
Matt, exactly.
这就是说，人们，当我们定义一个函数时，有两个部分。
And this is to say, people, when we
define a function, there's two parts.
这是我们的标识符，这是标签的华丽词汇
There's our identifier,
that is the fancy word for the label for
任何你存储在电脑内存里的东西。
anything you're storing
in computer's memory.
这里的标识符是 multilyby2。
The identifier here is multiplyBy2.
前面的标识符是 num。
The identifier before was num.
我最近学会了这个词，标识符。
I recently learned this word,
the identifier.
然后我们把所有的代码转换成函数,
And we then take all
the code to the function,
我们现在什么都不做。
we're not gonna run any of it right now.
我们要把它捆起来，存储在电脑的内存里
We're gonna take it, bundle it up and
store it in the computer's memory like
一个字符串，这个函数的所有代码。
a string of characters,
all the code of that function.
我不会把所有的代码都写出来，但是想象一下它们都保存在这里。
I'm not gonna write all that code up,
but literally imagine it all saved here.
相反，我要用这个小盒子代表它，里面有一个人渣
Instead, I'm gonna represent it
with this little box with an effin
表示函数。
that represents the function.
给你。
There you go.
好吧,
All right,
因此我们的执行线程，JavaScript 的奇特特性,
and therefore our thread of execution,
the fancy feature of JavaScript,
拿到密码，拿到密码，拿到密码，拿到密码，拿到密码。
that can take the code do it, take
the code, do it, take the code, do it.
现在我们来看看布拉登，它接下来会撞上什么？
Now we've down to where Braden,
what does it hit next?
扬声器3: 它定义了变量输出。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: It defines
the variable output.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，我要创造常量，人们似乎倾向于使用
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, I'm gonna create
constant, people tend to seem to be using
变量作为标签 + 数据、标识符 + 数据的通用术语，但是
variable as a generic term for,
Label + data, identifier + data, but
仔细想想，它的字面意思是，我可以改变存储在标签中的数据。
think about it, it literally means I can
vary the data that I store in that label.
对于一个常数，我不能改变，我不能拿走我以前储存在那里的东西
And with a constant, I can't vary, I can't
take away what I had stored there before
存储其他东西，稍后我们会详细讨论。
and store something else, and
we'll see more about that later on.
假设我们声明一个常量输出，非常好。
So let's say we declare a constant output,
excellent.
现在，Braden，我要在输出中存储什么？
Now Braden,
what am I gonna store in output?
我知道了吗？
Do I know yet?
讲者3: 没有。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
威尔 · 森特斯: 确切地说，我不知道,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I don't, exactly,
因为这个右手边是什么布莱登？
because this right hand
side is what Braden?
说话人3: 一个串行函数。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: A serial function.
威尔 · 森特斯: 是吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: It's?
讲者3: 函数调用。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Function call.
Will Sentance: 函数调用。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Function call.
来自丹的精彩，来自丹的精彩。
Excellent from Dan, excellent from Dan.
对函数的调用就是命令。
A call to a function is a command.
我只能存储固定的最终值。
I can only store values
that's fixed final things.
我不能存储指令，只能去做一些工作。
I can't store a instruction,
a go do some work.
丹，是什么告诉我右边这个是命令？
Dan, what tells me that this
right hand side is a command?
讲者3: 括号 威尔 · 句子: 括号，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Parentheses.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Parentheses, exactly.
完全正确。
Exactly right.
所以现在它仍然是未初始化的。
So then now it's gonna
remain uninitialized.
这与过去不明确的情况形成了对比，因为如果我们不得不这样做的话
This is in contrast to the old days where
it's undefined because again, if we had to
如果我们保存了这里没有定义的小数据，那么我们
carry our constant output, if we saved the
little data undefined here, well, then we
不能改变从函数返回的值。
wouldn't get to change it out for the
value that calls back from the function.
所以现在我们只能说它甚至没有完全储存在这里。
So now we just say it's not
really even fully stored here.
我要在这里展示，但是它还没有任何价值。
I'm gonna show it here, but
it's not got any value in it yet.
好吧，我们甚至不会，如果我们在运行和多个 by2尝试和
Okay, so we wouldn't even, if we were to
inside the running and multiplyBy2 try and
对数输出，我们不会看到未定义，我们只是看到它不在那里。
log output, we wouldn't see undefined,
we just see it's not there.
好了，当我们出发跑步的时候，乘以二，各位,
Okay, while we head off and
run, multiplyBy2, everybody,
准备好，因为这是 JavaScript 的一个很酷的特性。
be ready, because this is
the cool feature of JavaScript.
这是你们期待已久的时刻。
This is the moment that
you've all been waiting for.
我们打算用 num 的名字。
We're gonna call it with num.
Kayla num 的估值是多少变成多少？
Kayla, what does num evaluate to,
what value does it turn into?
讲者2:3 威尔 · 森塔斯: 3，等一下。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: 3.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: 3, hold on.